surveyreport.com 2015-08-06

# Survey Report - About Us

#### Privacy Policy

* * *

This Privacy Policy governs our policies and practices with respect to the personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") and other data that is collected by SurveyReport.com ("SurveyReport", "we", "us" and/or "our") in connection with our website, located at http://SurveyReport.com (the "Site") and our Facebook applications and related services (together with the Site, the "Service(s)").

By using our Services you are consenting to our processing of your Personal Information and data as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended. As used herein, "processing" means using or accessing information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, combining and disclosing information. By using our Services, you understand that your information may be transferred to our facilities and those third parties with whom we share it as described in this Privacy Policy.

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED

  * When you register an account to become a SurveyReport user (“User”), we collect your name, e-mail, phone number, industry, title/role, and skills.
  * Regardless of registration, by visiting our Site, we may place cookies on your computer, collect your IP address, browser type, operating system and receive the URLs of site from which you arrive or leave the SurveyReport website.
  * When you import your contacts using Gmail, Yahoo, Hotmail, Microsoft Exchange or other email/contact services, we receive names and email addresses of your contacts. You can choose to delete these, or have us invite them to your network on SurveyReport. We do not store any usernames or passwords that you choose to give us for 3rd-party contact services.
  * Registration to SurveyReport requires logging in via either a LinkedIn or Facebook account. This is to verify your identity, as well as access your professional work history. We do not store any usernames or passwords when you login using either of these services, and operate using the API guidelines and rules set forth by these services.
  * By logging in via Facebook, you must install the SurveyReport Facebook application first. This gives us access to your friends list, your personal profile picture, email, and your work history.
  * By logging in via LinkedIn, we collect your name, work history, email address and profile pic.

#### USES OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We use the information you provide to:

  * Enable you to share your information and communicate with other Users
  * Administer your account with us and customize the service we provide to you and other Users
  * Email you with updates on important account activity
  * Import or notify your contacts to interact with you
  * Share key milestones, such as an improvement in your Ranking, with your contacts & friends
  * Populate your profile with imported information such as picture, work history, name, location etc
  * Rank and compare you to other Users
  * Connect you to opportunities by enabling other professionals to find you
  * Use analytics software to see aggregate trends in how our Users use our Service
  * Enable you to send and receive ratings and manage your ranking
  * Allow search engines to find your ratings and reviews

####  WE DO NOT: 

We do not sell, rent, or otherwise provide personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent except where it is necessary to carry out your instructions (to process your payment information, for example) or as required by law. We also provide you with the means to control whether or not your contact information is viewable to other Users through your profile. 

####  YOUR INFORMATION CHOICES

You can:

  * Review, enhance or edit your personal information through your personal profile page; 
  * Control what information you make available to search engines through your public profile;
  * Choose whether you wish to login using Facebook or LinkedIn;
  * Change your settings to control visibility and accessibility through our website;
  * Tell us to delete your account;
  * Change how we notify you via email by managing your account settings;
  * Change how we interact with your contacts & friends by managing your account settings;
  * Do not abuse the SurveyReport service by using it to spam, abuse, harass, or otherwise violate the User Agreement or Privacy Policy.

#### SECURITY

Personal information you provide will be secured in accordance with industry standards and technology. Although we will try our best, since the internet is not a 100% secure environment, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Us. There is no guarantee that information may not be accessed, copied, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information, and for controlling access to your email communications at all times.

####  HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have questions or comments please send them to us here or contact us at:  
info@SurveyReport.com
